A Guide to the Kenneth Chorley papers FA067
Rockefeller Archive Center
Kenneth Chorley papers
1918-1976
Rockefeller Archive Center
Chorley, Kenneth
FA067
32 Cubic Feet 47 boxes
Conditions Governing Access
Open for scholarly research without restriction.
Arrangement note
The Kenneth Chorley papers are divided into four series:
Series 1 - Jackson Hole
Series 2 - Personal
Series 3 - Colonial Williamsburg
Series 1030 - Photographs
Biographical/Historical note
Conservationist and leader in the field of historic preservation, Kenneth Chorley was born in Bournemouth, England, on May 21, 1893, the son of Dr. Edward Clowes and Florence (Dover) Chorley. He moved to the United States with his family in 1900. He attended Manlius School in Manlius, New York, and received an honorary LL.D. from the College of William and Mary in 1934. In 1920, he married Elizabeth O'Kane, and they had two children. That marriage ended in divorce in 1941. Chorley married Jean Travers in 1941.
Prior to 1923, Chorley worked for the El Paso & Southwestern Railroad; the Detroit, Toledo & Ironton Railroad; and the Nevins Church Press. Kenneth Chorley began his long association with John D. Rockefeller, Jr. in 1923 when he became an associate of Arthur Woods in the Office of the Messieurs Rockefeller. In the ensuing years Chorley represented Mr. Rockefeller, Jr. in his numerous interests. Chorley was a staff member of the Laura Spelman Rockefeller Memorial from 1923-1928, and later of the Spelman Fund of New York (1928-1936).
Chorley was active in the restoration of Colonial Williamsburg from its inception in 1926 and worked closely with John D. Rockefeller, Jr. to recreate eighteenth-century Williamsburg as living history. He served as vice-president (1930-1935), treasurer (1934-1937), president (1935-1958), and director (1930-1963) of Williamsburg Restoration, Inc., and was a board member until his retirement in 1963. He was also trustee (1930-1963), vice-president (1930-1935), treasurer (1934-1937), and succeeded Arthur Woods as president (1935-1958) of Colonial Williamsburg, Inc., which holds title to nearly all the properties in the restored area and operates the exhibition buildings and all educational programs.
Mr. Chorley also served as Mr. Rockefeller, Jr.'s representative in the creation of Grand Teton National Park. Beginning in 1926, Chorley directed the Snake River Land Company's acquisition and conservation of over 33,000 acres of land in the Grand Tetons. The land was turned over to the National Park Service in 1949 as a part of Grand Teton National Park. Jackson Hole Preserve, Incorporated, which succeeded the Snake River Land Company, administered the land and the preserve. The Grand Teton Lodge Company, which succeeded the Grant Teton Lodge and Transportation Company, was the business corporation that operated visitor accommodations at the park. Both organizations were created in 1940. Chorley served as trustee (1940-1974), treasurer (1952-1955), and vice-president (1954-1964) of Jackson Hole Preserve, Inc., and president (1952-1963) of the Grand Teton Lodge Company.
Kenneth Chorley died March 21, 1974.
Scope and Contents note
The Kenneth Chorley papers contain correspondence, financial records, minutes, legal documents, reports, clippings, and photographs relating to the development of Colonial Williamsburg and Jackson Hole, Wyoming, as well as to Chorley's professional activities in the field of historic preservation. Most of the collection relates to his business activities; there are few personal papers.
Related Archival Materials note
For additional information on Jackson Hole, Wyoming, see also the Harold P. Fabian papers and the Rockefeller Family Archives, Record Group 2, Cultural Interests series.
For additional information on Colonial Williamsburg, see also the Rockefeller Family Archives, Record Group 2, Cultural Interests series; and the Colonial Williamsburg Foundation Archives, located in Williamsburg, Virginia.
File Plan note
Former Classification: IV 3A 03
Immediate Source of Acquisition note
The papers of Kenneth Chorley were deposited at the Rockefeller Archive Center by Jean Travers Chorley in 1976 and 1977 and were donated to the Center in 1979.
Physical Characteristics and Technical Requirements
Materials requiring specialized equipment for access (film, audio, video, slides) may be closed to research dependent on availability of the applicable equipment
Brittle or damaged items, or materials otherwise in need of preservation care, may be closed to researchers at the discretion of the RAC Head of Archival Services/Head of Reference.
Historic preservation; Water rights; Elk; Jackson Hole Wildlife Park; Yellowstone National Park; Restoration and conservation; Environmental policy; Grand Teton National Park (Wyo.); Jackson Hole (Wyo.); Rockefeller, John D. (John Davison); Jackson Hole Preserve, Incorporated; Chorley, Kenneth; Colonial Williamsburg (Williamsburg, Va.)
- Jackson Hole, 1926-1949; 1; 10 Cubic Feet
  Scope and Contents note
  This series contains correspondence, reports, financial records, and legal documents pertaining to the town of Jackson Hole, Wyoming; Jackson Hole Preserve, Inc.; the Snake River Land Company; JY Ranch; and the creation of Grand Teton National Park. Subjects include purchasing land for the Preserve, the proposed enlargement of Yellowstone and Grand Teton National Parks, Jackson Hole Wildlife Park, elk herds, water rights, and trips west by Chorley, the John D. Rockefeller, Jr. family and friends, Saunders Draper, Ed Kendrew, Arthur Woods, and Vanderbilt Webb.
  Arrangement note
  Records are maintained in their original order and are arranged alphabetically by subject.
  - Audit - Grand Teton Lodge and Transportation Company, 1946-1948 (Box 1, Folder 1)
    Related Archival Materials note
    See also Box 30, Folder 259.
  - Audit - Jackson Hole Preserve, Inc., 1946-1949 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Audit - Jackson Hole Wildlife Park, 1946-1949 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Barrett Bill, 1945-1947 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Barrett Bill - Buchenroth Compromise, 1947-1949 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Carhart Program, 1947-1949 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Carhart Program, 1947-1949 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Cr-De (Box 1, Folder 8)
    Crisp, Robert - 1938-1947 Dewey, Thomas E., Visit - 1947
  - Government Road, 1929-1931, 1940 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Grand Teton National Park, 1928-1931 (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - History, 1942 (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - Interoffice Correspondence, 1927-1934 (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - Interoffice Correspondence, 1927-1934 (Box 2, Folder 13)
  - Interoffice Correspondence, 1927-1934 (Box 2, Folder 14)
  - Izaak Walton League of America, 1945-1949 (Box 2, Folder 15)
  - Jackson Hole Airport, 1940-1943 (Box 2, Folder 16)
  - Jackson Hole Preserve, Inc. - Board of Trustees - Correspondence/Minutes, 1945-1948 (Box 2, Folder 17)
  - Jackson Hole Preserve, Inc. - Finances, Receipts and Disbursements, 1945-1948 (Box 2, Folder 18)
  - Jackson Hole Preserve, Inc. - Report - Recreational and Cultural Conservation, 1957 (Box 2, Folder 19)
  - Jackson Hole Wildlife Park - Meetings, 1945-1946 (Box 2, Folder 20)
  - Jackson Hole Wildlife Park - Publicity, 1945-1948 (Box 2, Folder 21)
  - Jackson State Bank, 1930-1933 (Box 3, Folder 22)
  - Legal Representative - Webb - Compensation and Expense Account, 1927-1929 (Box 3, Folder 23)
  - Maps, 1926-1932 (Box 3, Folder 24)
  - Meetings - Business and Social, 1927-1944 (Box 3, Folder 25)
  - Meetings - Business and Social, 1927-1944 (Box 3, Folder 26)
  - Meetings - Business and Social, 1927-1944 (Box 3, Folder 27)
  - Meetings - Business and Social, 1927-1944 (Box 3, Folder 28)
  - Memoranda (Box 3, Folder 29)
    Chorley - 1927-1928 Meyer - 1930-1931
  - Mo-Ph (Box 3, Folder 30)
    Mortgages - 1931 Motion Picture - 1940 Personnel - 1930, 1936-1937 Peterson Bill - 1945-1947 Photographs - 1929-1933
  - Plan, 1927-1931 (Box 4, Folder 31)
  - Plan, 1927-1931 (Box 4, Folder 32)
  - Plan, 1927-1931 (Box 4, Folder 33)
  - Plan, 1927-1931 (Box 4, Folder 34)
  - Plan, 1927-1931 (Box 4, Folder 35)
  - Plan, 1927-1931 (Box 4, Folder 36)
  - Plan, 1927-1931 (Box 4, Folder 37)
  - Plan, 1932-1934 (Box 5, Folder 38)
  - Plan, 1932-1934 (Box 5, Folder 39)
  - Plan, 1932-1934 (Box 5, Folder 40)
  - Plan, 1932-1934 (Box 5, Folder 41)
  - Plan, 1932-1934 (Box 5, Folder 42)
  - Plan, 1932-1934 (Box 5, Folder 43)
  - Plan, 1935-1943 (Box 6, Folder 44)
  - Plan, 1935-1943 (Box 6, Folder 45)
  - Plan, 1935-1943 (Box 6, Folder 46)
  - Plan, 1935-1943 (Box 6, Folder 47)
  - Plan, 1935-1943 (Box 6, Folder 48)
  - Plan, 1935-1943 (Box 6, Folder 49)
  - Plan, 1935-1943 (Box 6, Folder 50)
  - Plan (Box 7, Folder 51)
    Buffalo Herd - 1930 Condemnation - 1929
  - Plan - Elk Commission, 1929-1935 (Box 7, Folder 52)
  - Plan - Consultants - Burt, Stewart, 1927-1929 (Box 7, Folder 53)
  - Plan (Box 7, Folder 54)
    Forest Service Leases - 1928-1930 Hoover Visit - 1931 "Jackson Hole Courier" - 1931-1932, 1945
  - Plan - Jackson Hole Preserve, Inc., 1939-1943 (Box 7, Folder 55)
  - Plan - Jackson Hole Preserve, Inc., 1939-1943 (Box 7, Folder 56)
  - Plan - Jackson Hole Preserve, Inc. - Financing, 1941-1945 (Box 7, Folder 57)
  - Plan - Jackson Hole Preserve, Inc. - Minutes, 1940-1944 (Box 7, Folder 58)
  - Plan - Jackson Hole Preserve, Inc. - Property Transfer, 1940-1942 (Box 7, Folder 59)
  - Plan - Jackson Hole Program, 1930-1931, 1938 (Box 8, Folder 60)
  - Plan - Kendrew Reports, 1942-1943 (Box 8, Folder 61)
  - Plan - Legislation (Proposed), 1930 (Box 8, Folder 62)
  - Plan - Lion's Club, 1931-1933 (Box 8, Folder 63)
  - Plan - National Monument (Proposed), 1939-August 1943 (Box 8, Folder 64)
  - Plan - National Monument (Proposed), 1939-August 1943 (Box 8, Folder 65)
  - Plan - National Monument (Proposed), 1939-August 1943 (Box 8, Folder 66)
  - Plan - National Monument (Proposed), 1939-August 1943 (Box 8, Folder 67)
  - Plan - National Monument (Proposed), 1939-August 1943 (Box 8, Folder 68)
  - Plan - National Monument (Proposed), September 1943-1944 (Box 9, Folder 69)
  - Plan - National Monument (Proposed), September 1943-1944 (Box 9, Folder 70)
  - Plan - National Monument (Proposed), September 1943-1944 (Box 9, Folder 71)
  - Plan - National Monument (Proposed) - Preliminary Master Plan, 1943 (Box 9, Folder 72)
  - Plan - National Monument (Proposed) - O'Mahoney, 1943-1945 (Box 9, Folder 73)
  - Plan - Opposition, 1931, 1938-1939 (Box 9, Folder 74)
  - Plan - Property Transfer, 1942-1943 (Box 9, Folder 75)
  - Plan - Property Transfer - Budgets and Financial, 1942-1943 (Box 9, Folder 76)
  - Plan - Rockefeller, 1926-1932 (Box 9, Folder 77)
  - Plan - Senate Investigation, 1930-1932 (Box 9, Folder 78)
  - Plan - Senate Investigation, 1933-1934 (Box 10, Folder 79)
  - Plan - Senate Investigation, 1933-1934 (Box 10, Folder 80)
  - Plan - Senate Investigation, 1933-1934 (Box 10, Folder 81)
  - Plan - Senate Investigation, 1933-1934 (Box 10, Folder 82)
  - Plan - Senate Investigation, 1933-1934 (Box 10, Folder 83)
  - Plan - Senate Investigation, 1933-1934 (Box 10, Folder 84)
  - Plan - Senate Investigation, 1933-1934 (Box 10, Folder 85)
  - Plan - Senate Investigation, 1938 (Box 11, Folder 86)
  - Plan - Senate Investigation - Transcript (Yellowstone Boundary Revision), 1927 (Box 11, Folder 87)
  - Plan - Senate Investigation - Transcript (Yellowstone and Grand Teton Enlargement), Volume 1, 1933 (Box 11, Folder 88)
  - Plan - Senate Investigation - Transcript (Yellowstone and Grand Teton Enlargement), Volume 2, 1933 (Box 11, Folder 89)
  - Plan - Senate Investigation - Transcript (Yellowstone and Grand Teton Enlargement), Volume 3, 1933 (Box 11, Folder 90)
  - Plan - Senate Investigation - Transcript (Yellowstone and Grand Teton Enlargement), 1933 (Box 12, Folder 91)
  - Plan - Senate Investigation - Transcript (Grand Teton Enlargement), 1938 (Box 12, Folder 92)
  - Plan - Senate Investigation - Transcript (To Abolish Jackson Hole National Monument), 1943 (Box 12, Folder 93)
  - Plan - Senate Investigation - Transcript (To Abolish Jackson Hole National Monument), 1943 (Box 12, Folder 94)
  - Plan - Sheppard, 1930-1931 (Box 12, Folder 95)
  - Plan - Wyoming - House Bill #26, 1933 (Box 12, Folder 96)
  - Plan - Wyoming - State and School Lands, 1927-1933 (Box 12, Folder 97)
  - Power, 1929, 1940-1941 (Box 12, Folder 98)
  - Procedure, 1929-1932, 1943 (Box 12, Folder 99)
  - Property - Administration - Turner and Grace Situation, 1928-1929 (Box 12, Folder 100)
  - Property - Discrepancies, 1928 (Box 12, Folder 101)
  - Property - Discrepancies, 1929, 1935 (Box 13, Folder 102)
  - Property - Entries Pending, 1928-1934 (Box 13, Folder 103)
  - Property - Entries Pending, 1928-1934 (Box 13, Folder 104)
  - Property - Entries Pending, 1928-1934 (Box 13, Folder 105)
  - Property - Entries Pending, 1928-1934 (Box 13, Folder 106)
  - Property - Entries Pending, 1928-1934 (Box 13, Folder 107)
  - Property - Forms, 1928-1929 (Box 13, Folder 108)
  - Property - Leases, 1927-1944 (Box 13, Folder 109)
  - Property - Leases, 1927-1944 (Box 13, Folder 110)
  - Property - Management, 1928-1944 (Box 14, Folder 111)
  - Property - Management, 1928-1944 (Box 14, Folder 112)
  - Property - Management, 1928-1944 (Box 14, Folder 113)
  - Property - Management, 1928-1944 (Box 14, Folder 114)
  - Property - Management - Descriptions, 1929 (Box 14, Folder 115)
  - Property - Purchase - 41/116, 1930 (Box 14, Folder 116)
    41/116 is read as Township 41 North, Range 116 West of the 6th principal meridian.
  - Property - Purchase - 42/115, 1928-1934 (Box 14, Folder 117)
    42/115 is read as Township 42 North, Range 115 West of the 6th principal meridian.
  - Property - Purchase - 42/115 - Company Headquarters, Elbo, 1929-1944 (Box 14, Folder 118)
  - Property - Purchase - 42/115 - J.P. Ranch, 1927-1935 (Box 14, Folder 119)
  - Property - Purchase - 42/115 - Smith and Lovejoy, 1928-1930 (Box 15, Folder 120)
  - Property - Purchase - 42/116, 1928-1944 (Box 15, Folder 121)
    42/116 is read as Township 42 North, Range 116 West of the 6th principal meridian.
  - Property - Purchase - 42/116, 1928-1944 (Box 15, Folder 122)
  - Property - Purchase - 42/116, 1928-1944 (Box 15, Folder 123)
  - Property - Purchase - 42/116, 1928-1944 (Box 15, Folder 124)
  - Property - Purchase - 42/116 - J.Y. Ranch, 1931-1936 (Box 15, Folder 125)
  - Property - Purchase - 42/116 - J.Y. Ranch, 1931-1936 (Box 15, Folder 126)
  - Property - Purchase - 42/116 - J.Y. Ranch, 1937-1943 (Box 16, Folder 127)
  - Property - Purchase - 42/116 - J.Y. Ranch, 1937-1943 (Box 16, Folder 128)
  - Property - Purchase - 42/116 - J.Y. Ranch, Telephone Easement, 1940 (Box 16, Folder 129)
  - Property - Purchase - 42/116 (Box 16, Folder 130)
    McBride - 1928 Wells - 1944 42/116 is read as Township 42 North, Range 116 West of the 6th principal meridian.
  - Property - Purchase - 43/115, 1928-1937, 1942-1943 (Box 16, Folder 131)
    43/115 is read as Township 43 North, Range 115 West of the 6th principal meridian.
  - Property - Purchase - 43/115, 1928-1937, 1942-1943 (Box 16, Folder 132)
  - Property - Purchase - 43/115 - Bar B C Ranch, 1929-1942 (Box 16, Folder 133)
  - Property - Purchase - 43/115 - Bar B C Ranch, 1929-1942 (Box 16, Folder 134)
  - Property - Purchase - 43/115 - Ferrell, 1928-1929 (Box 16, Folder 135)
  - Property - Purchase - 43/116, 1928-1944 (Box 17, Folder 136)
    43/116 is read as Township 43 North, Range 116 West of the 6th principal meridian.
  - Property - Purchase - 43/116, 1928-1944 (Box 17, Folder 137)
  - Property - Purchase - 43/116, 1928-1944 (Box 17, Folder 138)
  - Property - Purchase - 43/116, 1928-1944 (Box 17, Folder 139)
  - Property - Purchase - 43/116 - Ferry Ranch, 1928-1930, 1937 (Box 17, Folder 140)
  - Property - Purchase - 43/116 - Post Office, 1929-1930 (Box 17, Folder 141)
  - Property - Purchase - 43//44/116, 1943-1944 (Box 17, Folder 142)
    43//44/116 is read as Township 43/44 North, Range 116 West of the 6th principal meridian.
  - Property - Purchase - 44/113, 1928-1933 (Box 17, Folder 143)
    44/113 is read as Township 44 North, Range 113 West of the 6th principal meridian.
  - Property - Purchase - 44/114, 1928-1943 (Box 18, Folder 144)
    44/114 is read as Township 44 North, Range 114 West of the 6th principal meridian.
  - Property - Purchase - 44/114 - Ferrin, 1928-1932, 1937-1938 (Box 18, Folder 145)
  - Property - Purchase - 44/115, 1928-1936 (Box 18, Folder 146)
    44/115 is read as Township 44 North, Range 115 West of the 6th principal meridian.
  - Property - Purchase - 44/115, 1928-1936 (Box 18, Folder 147)
  - Property - Purchase - 44/116, 1929-1930, 1939 (Box 18, Folder 148)
    44/116 is read as Township 44 North, Range 116 West of the 6th principal meridian.
  - Property - Purchase - 45/112, 1928-1929 (Box 18, Folder 149)
    45/112 is read as Township 45 North, Range 112 West of the 6th principal meridian.
  - Property - Purchase - 45/113, 1928-1934, 1940 (Box 18, Folder 150)
    45/113 is read as Township 45 North, Range 113 West of the 6th principal meridian.
  - Property - Purchase - 45/114, 1928-1930 (Box 18, Folder 151)
    45/114 is read as Township 45 North, Range 114 West of the 6th principal meridian.
  - Property - Purchase - 45/114, 1931-1944 (Box 19, Folder 152)
  - Property - Purchase - 45/114, 1931-1944 (Box 19, Folder 153)
  - Property - Purchase - 45/114 - Sheffield, 1928-1929 (Box 19, Folder 154)
  - Property - Purchase - 45/115, 1927 (Box 19, Folder 155)
    45/115 is read as Township 45 North, Range 115 West of the 6th principal meridian.
  - Property - Purchase - 46/113, 1929 (Box 19, Folder 156)
    46/113 is read as Township 46 North, Range 113 West of the 6th principal meridian.
  - Property - Purchase - 46/114, 1930 (Box 19, Folder 157)
    46/114 is read as Township 46 North, Range 114 West of the 6th principal meridian.
  - Property - Purchase - 46/115, 1930-1933, 1941 (Box 19, Folder 158)
    46/115 is read as Township 46 North, Range 115 West of the 6th principal meridian.
  - Property - Purchase - 46/116, 1930 (Box 19, Folder 159)
    46/116 is read as Township 46 North, Range 116 West of the 6th principal meridian.
  - Property - Purchase - Descriptions, 1928 (Box 19, Folder 160)
  - Property - Purchase - Jenny Lake Dance Hall, 1928-1931, 1937 (Box 19, Folder 161)
  - Property - Purchase - Jones, Winger, Eynon, 1927-1930 (Box 19, Folder 162)
  - Property - Purchase - Procedure, 1928-1929, 1935 (Box 19, Folder 163)
  - Property - Progress Reports, 1928-1930 (Box 19, Folder 164)
  - Property - Progress Reports, 1928-1930 (Box 19, Folder 165)
  - Property - Rockefeller, John D. Jr., 1943 (Box 19, Folder 166)
  - Property - Summaries and Reports (Monthly), 1928-1929 (Box 19, Folder 167)
  - Property - Summaries and Reports (Monthly), 1930-1933 (Box 20, Folder 168)
  - Property - Summaries and Reports (Monthly), 1930-1933 (Box 20, Folder 169)
  - Property - Summaries and Reports (Monthly) - Sophie Meyer, 1929-1931 (Box 20, Folder 170)
  - Property - Tax and Insurance, 1928-1944 (Box 20, Folder 171)
  - Publicity, 1927-1931 (Box 20, Folder 172)
  - Publicity, 1927-1931 (Box 20, Folder 173)
  - Publicity, 1927-1931 (Box 20, Folder 174)
  - Publicity, 1927-1931 (Box 20, Folder 175)
  - Publicity, 1932-1941 (Box 21, Folder 176)
  - Publicity, 1932-1941 (Box 21, Folder 177)
  - Publicity, 1932-1941 (Box 21, Folder 178)
  - Publicity, 1932-1941 (Box 21, Folder 179)
  - Publicity - Newspapers - "Grand Teton" - Correspondence Re, 1932-1934 (Box 21, Folder 180)
  - Publicity - Newspapers - "Grand Teton" - Articles, 1931-1941 (Box 21, Folder 181)
  - Publicity - Newspapers - "Grand Teton" - Articles, 1931-1941 (Box 21, Folder 182)
  - Publicity - Newspapers - "Grand Teton" - Articles, 1931-1941 (Box 21, Folder 183)
  - Publicity - Newspapers - "Grand Teton" - Articles, 1931-1941 (Box 21, Folder 184)
  - Publicity - Newspapers - "Jackson Hole Courier", 1932-1933 (Box 21, Folder 185)
  - Publicity - Newspapers - "Jackson Hole Courier" - Snake River Land Company - Letter re. History, 1932-1933 (Box 22, Folder 186)
  - Publicity - Newspapers - "Jackson Hole Courier" - Snake River Land Company - Letter re. History, 1932-1933 (Box 22, Folder 187)
  - Publicity - Newspapers - Miscellaneous Articles, 1933 (Box 22, Folder 188)
  - Publicity - Pamphlets (Box 22, Folder 189)
  - Reclamation, 1930-1932 (Box 22, Folder 190)
  - Rep-Sai (Box 22, Folder 191)
    Report - 1931 Routine - 1927-1930 St. John's Hospital - 1930-1941
  - Schedules, 1927-1932 (Box 22, Folder 192)
  - Schedules, 1927-1932 (Box 22, Folder 193)
  - Schedules, 1927-1932 (Box 22, Folder 194)
  - Sheep Memorial, 1929 (Box 23, Folder 195)
  - Snake River Land Company - Account - Construction, 1929-1930 (Box 23, Folder 196)
  - Snake River Land Company - Account - Operating, 1929-1941 (Box 23, Folder 197)
  - Snake River Land Company - Account - Operating, 1929-1941 (Box 23, Folder 198)
  - Snake River Land Company - Account - Operating, 1929-1941 (Box 23, Folder 199)
  - Snake River Land Company - Attorney, 1927-1933, 1945 (Box 23, Folder 200)
  - Snake River Land Company - Board of Directors - Minutes, 1940-1941 (Box 23, Folder 201)
  - Snake River Land Company - Compensation, 1927-1931 (Box 23, Folder 202)
  - Snake River Land Company - Dissolution, 1943 (Box 23, Folder 203)
  - Snake River Land Company - Expenses - Land Purchase, 1928-1932 (Box 23, Folder 204)
  - Snake River Land Company - Expenses - Legal and Other, 1927-1942 (Box 24, Folder 205)
  - Snake River Land Company - Expenses - Legal and Other, 1927-1942 (Box 24, Folder 206)
  - Snake River Land Company - Expenses - Legal and Other, 1927-1942 (Box 24, Folder 207)
  - Snake River Land Company - Expenses - Legal and Other, 1927-1942 (Box 24, Folder 208)
  - Snake River Land Company - Finances - Statements, 1928-1933 (Box 24, Folder 209)
  - Snake River Land Company - Finances - Statements, 1928-1933 (Box 24, Folder 210)
  - Snake River Land Company - Finances - Statements, 1928-1933 (Box 24, Folder 211)
  - Snake River Land Company - Finances - Statements, 1928-1933 (Box 24, Folder 212)
  - Snake River Land Company - Finances - Statements, 1934-1943 (Box 25, Folder 213)
  - Snake River Land Company - Finances - Statements, 1934-1943 (Box 25, Folder 214)
  - Snake River Land Company - Finances - Statements, 1934-1943 (Box 25, Folder 215)
  - Snake River Land Company - Finances - Statements, 1934-1943 (Box 25, Folder 216)
  - Snake River Land Company - Finances - Statements, 1934-1943 (Box 25, Folder 217)
  - Snake River Land Company - History, 1933 (Box 25, Folder 218)
    See also Box 30, Folder 264.
  - Snake River Land Company - Incorporation, 1927-1928 (Box 25, Folder 219)
  - Snake River Land Company - Real Estate, 1930-1936 (Box 25, Folder 220)
  - Snake River Land Company - Real Estate - Agent - Miller, 1927-1928 (Box 25, Folder 221)
  - Snake River Land Company - Real Estate - Agent - Miller, 1929-1931 (Box 26, Folder 222)
  - Snake River Land Company - Real Estate - Agent - Winger, 1930-1935, 1941-1943 (Box 26, Folder 223)
  - Telephone and Telegram Lines, 1931-1933, 1941 (Box 26, Folder 224)
  - Teton Companies - Moran Development, 1936-1945 (Box 26, Folder 225)
  - Teton Companies - Sale Proposed, 1931 (Box 26, Folder 226)
  - Teton County Study, 1946 (Box 26, Folder 227)
  - Teton Lodge Company - Concessions, 1929-1934 (Box 26, Folder 228)
  - Teton Lodge Company - Franchise - Transportation, 1929-1930 (Box 26, Folder 229)
  - Teton Lodge Company - Jackson Lake Lodge, 1929-1932 (Box 26, Folder 230)
  - Teton Lodge Company - Moran Development, 1929-1935 (Box 27, Folder 231)
  - Teton Lodge Company - Moran Development, 1929-1935 (Box 27, Folder 232)
  - Ticklers, 1943-1944 (Box 27, Folder 233)
  - Township Plats, 1927-1930 (Box 27, Folder 234)
  - Water Rights, 1935-1943 (Box 27, Folder 235)
  - Water Rights, 1935-1943 (Box 27, Folder 236)